http://www.oecd.org/privacy/

Privacy Policy - OECD
Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD)
Honduras
Hong Kong (China)
Luxembourg
Macau (China)
Paraguay
China (People’s Republic of)
Serbia
Serbia and Montenegro (pre-June 2006)
Topics
Agriculture and fisheriesChemical safety and biosafetyCompetitionCorporate governanceCorruption and integrityDevelopmentDigitalEconomyEducationEmploymentEnvironmentFinanceGreen growth and sustainable developmentHealthIndustry and entrepreneurshipInnovationInsurance and pensionsInvestmentMigrationPublic governanceRegional, rural and urban developmentRegulatory reformScience and technologySocial and welfare issuesTaxTrade
Coronavirus (COVID-19)
OECD Home
About
Countries
Afghanistan
Albania
Algeria
Andorra
Angola
Honduras
Hong Kong (China)
Hungary
Iceland
India
Indonesia
Iraq
Ireland
Iran
Isle of Man
Luxembourg
Macau (China)
Madagascar
Malawi
Malaysia
Maldives
Mali
Malta
Marshall Islands
Mauritania
Paraguay
China (People’s Republic of)
Peru
Philippines
Bolivia
Poland
Portugal
Puerto Rico
Qatar
Moldova
Serbia
Serbia and Montenegro (pre-June 2006)
Seychelles
Sierra Leone
Singapore
Slovak Republic
Slovenia
Solomon Islands
Somalia
South Africa
Topics
Agriculture and fisheriesChemical safety and biosafetyCompetitionCorporate governanceCorruption and integrityDevelopmentDigitalEconomyEducationEmploymentEnvironmentFinanceGreen growth and sustainable developmentHealthIndustry and entrepreneurshipInnovationInsurance and pensionsInvestmentMigrationPublic governanceRegional, rural and urban developmentRegulatory reformScience and technologySocial and welfare issuesTaxTrade
Coronavirus (COVID-19)
Français
OECD Home
Privacy Policy
The OECD is committed to protecting the personal data of users of its websites, which are an essential tool for advancing our mission and programme of work.
This privacy policy describes the types of personal data we collect, how we use it, who has access and for how long. It also provides information on the rights provided to website users under our data protection rules. Some activities supported by our websites are further subject to specific data protection notices (e.g. recruitment).
How we collect and use personal data
We collect personal data through the use of our websites in two ways: data you directly provide to us and data generated by your activity on the websites.
Data you directly provide. You can choose to voluntarily provide us personal data in the context of registering, subscribing to online newsletters and making purchases. This data enables us to provide the services you have requested and may include your name, physical address, email address, phone number.
Data generated by your activity. In order to ensure the effective functioning and security of our websites and to better understand visitor behavioural patterns, as you browse our websites we automatically collect:
Log information such as the pages you visit, the time/date of your visit as well as your internet prototcol (IP) address.
Device and software information such as your browser specifications and operating system
This information is collected through the use of various technologies, including cookies which are small text files stored in your browser. If you have registered and are logged-in, your browsing activity is linked to your user credentials so that we can personalise your experience on our websites, including for future visits.
Access and storage
In general, access to your personal data is limited to appropriate staff within the organisation. In some circumstances we make your data available outside the OECD, such as for:
Payment processing: We use a third-party service, PayPal, USA to process online payments.
Analytics: We use third-party services Google Analytics, USA, CXSense, Norway, and CrazyEgg, USA to help us understand visitor behaviour by allowing the service access to the data generated by your activity and store it using cookies. This data is processed in a way that does not directly identify you.
Email communications: We use third party services Adestra Upland Platform, UK, and MailChimp, USA for sending bulk email communications such as newsletters, platform alerts, and event notifications. These services store contact information that you provide to us via MyOECD as well as information about your interactions with these emails; such as opens and clicks.
Online surveys: We occasionally use Checkbox Survey, USA to run online surveys of user views.
Online communities: We use third party services, Zapnito, UK to provide you online networking environments. These services store contact information that you provide and data generated by your activity and store it using cookies.
Data you provide directly is typically kept until either (1) you unsubscribe from the service requested or until (2) two years after your last transaction. We store data about your activity on our websites for two years, after which time it is deleted. We keep data on email activity for two years, after which time it is deleted.
Links to other websites
Where we provide links to websites of other organisations, this privacy policy does not cover how those organisations processes personal data. For example, we link to our profiles on a number of social media platforms such as Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn, Instagram and YouTube. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or content on third-party websites and encourage you to read the privacy notices of other websites you visit.
How to contact us or exercise your rights
Under our data protection rules, you have rights to access and rectify your personal data, as well as to object to its processing, request erasure, and obtain data portability in certain circumstances. To exercise these rights in connection with your use of this website please contact webmaster@oecd.org.
If you have further queries or complaints related to the processing of your personal data, please contact the Data Protection Officer [dpo@oecd.org]. If you need further assistance in resolving claims related to personal data protection you can contact the Data Protection Commissioner [dpc@oecd.org].
Additional information about our approach to data protection is available here.
Follow us (Social Media):
